Contact

denelliott@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/denise-elliott-723788155 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Proficient at direct patient care within perioperative environment

Professional, effective communication

Proficient with EPIC and PICIS EHR's

Certifications

Certified Professional Coder

Denise Elliott

Field Reviewer at Change Healthcare

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

I am an RN/CPC seeking an opportunity to combine 25 years of nursing experience with my knowledge of coding and abstracting as a CPC-A. I am skilled with both written and verbal professional communication and documentation. I feel strongly about personal integrity and dependability and look forward to bringing these attributes into the workplace.

Experience

Change Healthcare
Field Reviewer
March 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months)
Alpharetta, Ga.

U.T. M.D.Anderson Cancer Center R.N. C.N.O.R. November 2012 - July 2017 (4 years 9 months) Houston, Texas 77030

Operating Room nurse -Specializing in perioperative care for all patients in the Ophthalmology, Head & Neck, Reconstructive Plastic Surgery, and Dental services. Professional communication/coordination with physicians, mid-levels, managers, vendors, etc. relating to the efficient function of the Ophthalmology surgical department. Helped to develop the Ophthalmology portion of the intraoperative record in EPIC. Clinical documentation in EPIC.

Kelsey Seybold ASC - Main Campus RN - Operating Room Staff Nurse April 2011 - November 2012 (1 year 8 months) Houston, Texas 77030

Provided perioperative care to surgical patients in all services within the operating room. Clinical documentation with PICIS (OR Manager)

The Methodist Hospital - TMC R.N. C.N.O.R.

April 1989 - September 2000 (11 years 6 months)

6565 Fannin Houston, Tx. 77030

Operating Room - Provided perioperative nursing care and clinical documentation for all Ophthalmic surgical procedures. Also served as Laser Safety Coordinator/Dept. Liaison. Rotated to other services as necessary.

St. Joseph's Hospital R.N. Staff Operating Room August 1977 - December 1983 (6 years 5 months) Houston, Texas

Service Coordinator for Plastic Surgery Department. Circulated all surgical services.

Education

AAPC

Certificate, Medical Insurance Coding Specialist/Coder · (2017)

San Jacinto College

Associate of Science - AS, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse